[Music]
showed me freely
oh back to the scrap ape
ready they're taking the point time to
blow it them up I meant them
well I'm at g'day
stop the payload I'm on the attack yeah
I'm sure I don't know anything you're
talking about three two one
we don't have all they move the payload
I'll be on me best behavior if at first
you don't succeed blow it up again just
when things were starting to get
interesting ah cheers mate g'day cover
today's a good day for some Mayhem
you're dreaming I think I could have a
look at one of those bombs of yours oh
that was a close one I'm on defense you
won't get rid of me that easily take out
the target
ding hey where'd that come from there
she blows
in three two one
piece of junk what's your head oh that's
where I left it I've got a leg up on the
competition
but it's just one nah find the
teleporter now that's a knife
yeah collateral damage that was the bomb
holy Dooley Moss incoming I'm with you
now that was beautiful no no no they're
moving the pilot stop them clear the
area let's sit up here and on that
bombshell too close too close Okay fall
back
[Laughter]
something tells me this movie's gonna
bomb
oh
I owe you one thumbs away brings tears
to me eyes four I knew there was a
reason I kept you around and it wasn't
the smuggling conversation
ah much better oh I could use this tick
tock tick tock tick tock
bye
[Laughter]
laughs
thank you
ah
press the attack
come true
[Laughter]
laughs
[Music]
[Applause]
just dead
I can't lose your head on my way come on
let me push it attack the objective oh
cheers all patched up defend the
objective payloads Moving Out All Aboard
catch you later you dipstick go
Rocky ladies and gentlemen
such your engines
I I'm the only one who gets to kill the
big log thanks mate start the victory
timer it won't be long now
stay right there I've got something for
you remember remember what the heck was
I saying again flaming Gala you got it
all in one enemy turret over there
what do we have here
g'day mate I'm taking the objective
anyone else want some no no no the pilot
stopped
tick tock tick tock so we're delivering
a bomb to scrap some Bots and I'm
getting paid for it my kind of job I
could always count on you mate my
ultimate's ready patience patience push
the payload I need healing
shiny if I had a PhD they'd call me Dr
boom you I believe a joke I'll big face
over there told me the other day a road
hog everyone stop the payload try not to
get us killed out there haha almost got
me it's truth
you look like the kind of guy who could
use something blown up join up with me
no
hahaha
[Laughter]
I need some armor
they've got a teleporter somewhere guess
we know who's really on top daily the
clock's ticking attack attack that was a
good one mate why is the payload stopped
clocks ticking we need to pump the
brakes on the payload moving the payload
clear a path oh you really stepped in it
mate push forward where'd everybody go
oh
no need to thank me okay mine mine mine
this is my point I need Shields junkrat
primed and ready gotcha don't you come
the raw prawn with me tick tock tick
tock tick tock tick tock attack attack
get ready enemy tourists just blew up
we got this just hold on a little longer
time is money friends and we're almost
flat broke
I don't mind me I was just taking five
definitely not thinking about blowing
something up no way definitely not
okay come on maybe just a little
something Rest In Pieces that point
belongs to us defend it much better
the point under attack let's give them
something to think about ah aiming's
overrated move it move it move it sniper
ah
back for more help now we're cooking
with gas ta tick tock tick tock we gotta
win looks like a Target Rich environment
Right On Target or better well
you know enemy teleport a Scrat takes a
licking keeps on ticking no idiot now
we're talking the point is mine and you
can't have it don't mind if I do or I
could use some help here I love it when
that happens what a bunch of Misfits and
freaks we got here I love it in three
two one I never get tired of this
well that's a fine how do you do
see ya looks like they were just playing
dead
ouch be on their teleporter time to blow
it up come on come on come on I hate
waiting behind you at this rate I'll be
the last man standing happy birthday
Riptide ready to roll you're making it
easy for me let's keep this payload
rolling I'm going in fire in the hall
it's hard to just sit around knowing
there's someone out there that needs to
be blown up boom
I love my job over there over there
oh
[Laughter]
Party Time need some fireworks group up
well I never like them anyways group up
here my genius is finally recognized
I won I won what did I win that's cold
brings a tear to my eye I give it a
three if at first you don't succeed blow
it up again
ah remember that time we stole the crown
jewels all hail King Jameson Fox the
first and uh Duke right hog what is your
name anyways dipstick hey where'd you go
you're blowing up why is it serious
cheers mate the cavalry's here the enemy
teams down for the count
Kaboom I beg your pardon I consider
myself a freedom fighter a misunderstood
one if these Bots want to go into the
light I'd be more than happy to help
group up with me how about some armor we
need a Healer need healing how about
some Shields over here my rip tire is
almost ready my rip tire is charging my
ultimate is charging my ultimate is
almost ready my ultimate is ready time
for some Mayhem
thank you thank you thank you oh I'm not
about to pack it in let's win this one
forget about that last round let's go
win this one more win that's all we need
peace okay we got this after all that
work let's not throw it away now it's
all tied up you know what that means
time for sudden death
oh I get cold just looking at you and I
thought I was supposed to be the comic
relief you hook them I'll cook them you
think there's something worth stealing
in that Temple I'm on fire
someone better get a fiery because I'm
on a roll oops drop something find us
keepers
just look at this beauty
sure I give it a 10. enemy team's been
wiped out now that's what I call an
explosion get out of there going up
everything's coming up explodey it's the
little things have a nice day anyone
want some barbecue
smile
[Laughter]
early bird gets the worm I'm on fire
usually there would not be a good thing
and they said I was the Mad one ladies
and gentlemen my latest creation
that must have been a real shock
damn it useless he called my inventions
not so useless now
you're not loving now are you I must
return to my lab but don't worry I will
return maybe we could work something out
mate
and I'll cook them get ready for a shock
life do you hear me
my creation live
oops
you show them roadhog sorry about that
fire not good electrifying
he's alive he's alive
you're welcome
I gotta get me one of those
God would kill for some boba milk tea
half sweet I'd say we forget about all
this and that other Beach instead many
takers
anyone
no
I hate to break this to everyone but if
we're here to blow up the Bots someone's
beating us to it
this is not my kind of weather anyone
have an extra coat or some mittens I
would kill for some mittens this place
is a bit Posh for me my New Year's
resolutions I think I'd like to travel
more I'm unstoppable
there's no one to stop me now
don't mention it go forth my monster
Kill Them All
you will all regret to die you laughed
at Dr James and junkenstein
do you like my creations
happy Halloween
happy holidays
seasons greetings
Merry Christmas
good morning
Happy Valentine's Day
Happy New Year
something's not right
not feeling good
enemy detected come out come out
wherever you are now that's the holiday
spirit oopsies
[Laughter]
they've got our flag after them I don't
know will it make me go he he
oh he's babe
my mistake just kidding I meant to do
that put some air on that one didn't I
hooroo mate does this make me Queen
Finders Keepers I'll take that don't
mind if I do come on so I was like
roadhog mate just cause that's how you
see it doesn't mean that's how she sees
it right Buddha never my Bastion let's
get out there
lovely armor for a mission isn't it now
I know I ain't got many mates among this
group but I hope we can look past our
differences and proceed forward with
mutual respect into a bold and
prosperous future inclusive of a few
modest explosions as the circumstances
permit Feast Your Eyes Upon This hand
curated assortment of tasteful
pyrotechnic Delights with which I intend
to entertain you this evening or
possibly morning what time is it this
way over it we'll have to blast our way
through
blow up that door what is an obstacle
it's not something begging to be blown
up knock it down and let's slide on
through come on we haven't got all day
that's awesome incoming oh there she is
watch out assassin making a dash for it
get that assassin before I Sizzle me
Dundas
assassin if you can hear me I'm covered
in bombs you probably want one of me
might an assassin ah no they've got an
enforcer I see an enforcer
more of those Talon blokes ahead we
almost got him just a little more
come on let's finish him off
sniper heads up there's a sniper got it
I am officially bored okay that's enough
waiting come on let's go let's go let's
go
what are we waiting on way more metal
than me you and I why we could be twins
I don't see you where'd you go where'd
she go got the Assassin no thanks to you
a lot the Assassin down well that was
stressful assassin down oh
oh no no
no my entrails it tickles get her off
get her off oh you're an assassin oh not
a bad feeling we're being hunted we'll
get a quick someone I'm begging you kill
that assassin she's on you mate she's
coming right by you and force her down
blew up an enforcer
that's what you get for trying to
enforce oh go and force yourself
oh he's still standing blow him up
not that heavy his continued survival
offends me
at this point I'm just curious how much
he can take get over here you lazy
things I found the objective come take a
look let's get on with it come on come
on come on all right let's move along
this way come on
hi champ why have you got that wombat
running around with you
and I'm president of the Moon seriously
though what's he for how many of you
OverWatch people are missing an eye
don't be so hard on yourself had me
breaking a billabong midnight was short
but my day was long
hi I want a mission too you looking for
a lab assistant I'm great with chemicals
oh what's pain have to do with science I
like what you got going on the ghost
Powers the magically replenishing
shotguns the mysterious identity you're
a real character what's on your mind
mate what's your keys the arrows snacks
I've got snacks cheer up ah but I wanted
to watch the footy you can't scare me
I'm
that one doesn't count uh champ which of
your glorious victories who was your
favorite mine was when you beat three
I'm Luke oh you gave him the what for
the champ himself can you sign me
forehead
ah but it's me specialty oh thank you
very much oh no he heard me this is so
awkward hey rocket lady did I make that
suit in my size why not I was born to
fly
would that help I don't do problems just
Solutions you look like a man who
inherited a vast Trove of ostentatious
wealth
I got this rash that won't go away I've
tried everything radiation dirt
radioactive dirt a sausage roll and
about itself that's what I would like to
have look
the strangest spot I've ever seen that's
all I'm saying hi dorbs can we trade
arms a sausage roll and a bad and Sam
that's what I hear would like to have
Jameson Fox and tour bjornland home two
handsome Geniuses just hit chatting away
payloads moving ah the Queen's gonna
love this
at least I'm not a hog oh no not as good
we should keep our heads down but I want
the paparazzi finding us who the bot I
thought he was decorative look at us two
superstars out in a bat
I sing Love
[Music]
doomfist Doom assist
it's a great name they call me junkrat
get this more bombs this is the
discipline the commander is known for
United again the OverWatch Strike Team
prepares for Action my queen your voice
ever sonorous is like a gentle waterfall
upon my ears
we should do a concert together
bombs was was there supposed to be
another step
ah bomb blastic Oh did a bomb get you a
scintillating finish
I impress myself sorry about that love
what you do with the dynamite monkey see
monkey die
die never mind oh no I blew up a fossil
yo misunderestimated me
couldn't you just fly away where are we
manners that's why I'm famous blown up
blown up
what do you think of my inventions wait
I got the doomfist guys I killed the
doomfist
howdy cow person
all right that one in my diary
sorry old friend we could have had a
beautiful partnership never meet your
Heroes get down from there if I can't
fly you're not allowed either junkrat
hero of anti-air defense
fisticuffs dunk clean here clean it wonk
ride in the griddle
someone get the camera
multifarious eliminations
[Laughter]
how many was that oh my stars
ding dong got you back
that's what you get for junking with
Nazareth wait a minute guys around comes
around mate dear diary today I blew up
several people in a rattle
I'm having a memorable Time bar
protected poetry
thank you for your patronage right on
time I accept all major currencies
got the whole Brigade
a historic rat Razzle Dazzle that's a
wipe
love the energy mate I like what you're
up to they missed with the wrong primate
Bullseye just like a western
Grandma's still got it
you got them good there great work champ
support your local Bombardier plenty of
bombs to go around I promise to take
this one serious oh I'm so excited I
brought the fireworks
Cannonball time to share me gifts with
the world pools open I'm jumping in you
little Ripper and around we go tired of
me yet
entirely unavoidable
rolled over burn in rubber caught
beneath the whale of progress that tire
popped you this situation calls for more
bombs buckle my shoe there's my hymn to
do
let's give it a fair Shake mate oh I'm
ready I ain't quitting can't keep a bad
lad down such perverty could not go
unanswered I'm going back in I still
think we can win I'll keep trying till I
run out of Limbs I am in the fatabago
this will tickle their feet
ooh can't wait
shh don't tell anyone this trap
exclusive property I have Jameson Fox
trapped snap gotcha oh likewise likewise
some of my favorite bombs are
extraordinarily precise
blasting off we have liftoff
if mum Could See Me Now
bon voyage
I want to push the button let's go let's
go
stop hitting myself blah
wow jackpot
I made that bomb myself
Peter Piper picked a pip no Peter Piper
picked up
how come you don't stay a big black all
the time fly my little friend the
pleasure is mine hold this a minute what
a lob
buying an explosive development works
every time terms and conditions May
apply concussion
scattered to the wind
my mistake
half the time works every time why have
I got this Detonator again waiting
waiting
no you're in a pickle
snagged yes
I sing
[Music]
all right
snapped out of the sky
dry
stealing is my favorite role is a list
of the things I stole diamonds and rules
magic Jewels expensive prosthodontitools
fancy bikes and shirts with spots hurts
exotic Wildlife cash and gold and all
that muck once I stole a fire truck
foreign
[Laughter]
I will return
four legs aren't better than one
never liked how I know the doctor we
need to protect our flag no get our flag
back land it all along just how I drew
it up I'm alive
go on give it a shake inconspicuous
really blew that one bet you never
thought you'd see pigs fly
Queen couldn't have done better herself
home field advantage you know
someone grabbed the flag it's just
sitting there someone take that flag
let's take the flag that's what happens
when you cross junkrats and roadhog they
said I was mad
me mad
remember the plan you know I never would
have taken you for someone with such a
homely home what do you think of that
your majesty
don't answer that I'm hurt I am nothing
if not a courteous house guest Jameson
Fox minister of engineering has a
certain ring to it home sweet home
that's not the chancellor but the price
is right I've been all around the world
and there's no way that compares to home
treasure secured trolley loaded they'll
never suspect a thing or one last time
we take this innocent pile of ill-gotten
treasure to the scrapyard reveal it to
the queen then boom rise and shine but
dime a dozen now who's got the ashes
still Treading Water I'm still kicking
don't forget your sunscreen Sun's
terrible for your skin
well it's a little cold I'm ready for
some fun in the sun Surf's Up Up
Cannonball time to jam the waters oh hi
matey tick tock tick tock tick tock tick
tock tick tock Captain junkrat ready to
set sail how's that you're a real
lifesaver
everyone out of the pool help that mate
you look like a gentleman who ate his
own toy Nails just looking for something
we might have in common
ah xenos Paradox oh I was just trying to
make a milkshake a bomb drop in a
package the sky is mine I'm just like
you rocket lady if I was always jumping
around try chucking the mine that's why
I never get mad clear to judgment
Abacus nice
circumstances would die Jameson's Health
was alarmingly low and then
[Laughter]
I like to maintain some distance from me
victims it's just good practice I hate
ghost especially when they do that
another hog fight for the Cerulean
Chancellor thanks for holding him down
that hammer was scary when he does that
twirly thing I find it best to stand a
very long way away
he was right there with the sword did
you see that I mean it was right there
I'm more dangerous when I'm hurt like a
corned pheasant I'm a bullion and so I
proceeded directly to a kill streak how
many kills for an invite to OverWatch
alert alert hey watch it keep your eyes
peeled
someone wise and experienced an adoptive
mother if you will that's why I'm an
artist
why would someone do that unless they
had a brilliant plan wouldn't decide be
more on brand can't really Harvest with
them but who am I to argue with Jeff
himself
thanks to the second most intimidating
person I know
hard to tell right from wrong if only I
had someone to give me guidance
demolition by Jameson
self-defeating
diegetic lies alike accuracy that's how
I do it son Anthony sends his regards
among the most deadly Australian porner
is the junker Town jumping bean Lads for
not taking me to space when I asked and
did somebody put a humiliating end to
your schemes
you were ultimately not successful I see
your leap and raise you a punch Against
All Odds the captain Falls to The Cheeky
upstart that's right I'm her favorite
child well I can't miss and what I do
miss it doesn't count I got the Imposter
your majesty I'd always recognize my
true Queen
unfortunately I know all our fighting
spots why detect them when you can blow
them up my launcher can't miss either
my dungeon me I've got a prognosticated
mind thought I'd give you an extra boost
there naughty out of the satellite a bit
of a spur in the rear right let's give
them the what for
open fire sure you don't want to adopt
me on it
it's a demolitionist derby
I've got a sound hundred they're
numerically Superior yikes
can I camp that high
uh personally I think my big moment was
bigger than your Big Moment by far the
stiff upper lip now you've come back
from worse rat jokes back I mean the
junkrats back is it snowing I really
love it when it snows come on Jameson
this is your big chance to impress
OverWatch am I the first one back oh
that's classic me alone again such
woeful Tidings oh where are my fellow
rapscallions rhodo I got ya hey shove
the boss let's move that robot let's all
push together now their push stop it
please stop the robot we must hold the
robot still feeling on my tire I'm
eyeballing it I've always had a gift for
fire
you're not good enough that easy
spotted it at nighter not quite the same
as one of mine they're coming up from
behind enemy dropped our flag what an
unpleasant development no way how'd they
do that huntage in the flag someone else
can take it from here drop the flag my
arms are getting tired
set off those fireworks I've captured
the flag I'm getting the feeling they
have a shield generator guess they
didn't want it that much
I found this Shield generator Eradicator
spotted slicer incoming watch your arms
and legs slash is incoming keep your
arms and legs inside the vehicle oh my
dog is barking their Shield generator
just went Kaboom Look Out Below enemy's
got the flag let's
blow it up I have the flag I have the
flag enemies behind us they're coming
from above I'm done for I'm hit it's an
hour 14. get ready for a fight no
Trooper let's scrap them don't suppose
you'd like to trade fists I mean they've
got our flag after them and I thought
I'd taken my legs it really makes you
wonder don't you think I think I can see
my trailer down there I'm hurt pretty
bad Flags going back to base now what's
that doing sitting around I've got the
flag now what I admire the way you deal
with those butts wanna team up
spotted it didn't either wow I need one
of those defend the objective tick tock
tick tock we gotta win start the victory
timer it won't be long now I'm taking
the objective anyone else want some is
it the bombs you don't like the bombs oh
farewell goodbye uh dropped it again did
I
where'd it go anybody got that I've been
thinking about leaving Society just me a
little cottage and all the gold bars I
can carry take me down to junkertown
where the grass is brown and the sky is
brown hit the one that's in the Trap
they're vulnerable get him got him let's
pile on they got Huggy don't die on me
you big lug Save the Queen or it's off
with our heads our friends in a
Gloucester pickle our teammate needs to
be revived who's gonna revive the
roadkill oh who wants to do CPR what a
place this is a ghost in every Havoc
maybe this is where I'll retire great
job keep pushing all right right making
progress we're in the ladies
yippee that's just the lead let's get it
back come on we've gotta push it further
than that uh we lost the lead come on
let's get it back
moving right along let her most
momentous push Cummins let's get this
party rolling
don't let him push it they're moving the
barricade stop them it's moving the
wrong way Houston we have the robot
robots in our position this robot really
knows how to walk they took the robot
give it back
hey I thought that robot was on our side
why they got the robot get it back
are they catching up oh we gotta stop
them it's time dust up the enemy they're
taking a swing let's push them back oh
we're so close I can smell it just a
little more just a little more just show
them a bit we've almost got the lead
stop them now and we win it's their last
chance let's stop them dead
they think they still have a chance
stick by the robot and he won't let us
down last chance Amigos make it
memorable
steady Last Chance let's make a count so
did you have a chance to think about my
proposal what oh no no no no no you
misunderstood I was talking about your
Shield
sticky bums what a fantastic idea how do
they work no worries I'll figure it out
on my own all I need is some glue one
stick of dynamite well that's just
adorable I meant admirable admirable
Jameson Force reporting live let's ask
this scary metal bloke how he thinks the
battle's gonna go boring back to you
Natasha any car chases we could watch
could you repeat that in words hold on a
breaking news the moon has fallen into
the ocean the Jameson Fox channel 9 news
Mr GunBot sir how do you think the
battle's gonna go I am junkrat and you
just died to junkrat I did it mum I'm on
fire
my fuses are alive look who's on fire
again me glowing like a junker Town
double cab
they can't stop me now
Unstoppable
push push with friends like these who
needs I love kinds of friends if you
really think about it bugs are just
little plants that move oh torbjorn I
ought to kiss you atop your sweet little
head anybody got a toothpick
got one of them mantis arms stuck
between me molars junkrats come to the
crease bit of an agricultural shot got
you with a googly ladies and gentlemen
he's working on a Century well that's
that oh you're not getting away get to
the objective we need to get together
before we can move on moving the
objective make way make way you're
coming right at you looks like we're
making progress they're coming right at
us looks like it's all up to me
objectives gonna blow up sooner or later
come on we're running out of time no
point in beating around the bush time is
money friends and we're almost flat
broke the objective is mine oh mine
objectives taken damage ah objectives
not looking so good
oh my God all gummed up together in a
big pile when I try I do stop them I
think my problem is that I stop them a
little too huh oh why OverWatch you'll
never take me alive
fan mail you get it I get it well I get
a lot of it I guess they love me out
there in this big crazy world
I want to write a novel they said no
Jameson you're not the type to write a
novel well I said watch me things always
go well when you're working with junkrat
and roadhog I got me eye on this
position watching this spot like a
conifer's hawk why I'm watching here
keeping an eye out sorry sorry there's
an enemy here Daddy over here oh almost
dropped me launcher sorry I've just got
nerves fighting alongside the champ if I
was a Greek god I'd be dying Dion the
one with the graves
hello
g'day get over here thanks mate ah
Cheers Cheers love it's time to save the
world that's what I'm always saying a
couple kind of hits
I'm a direct hit machine
they're all Landing today get ready for
a shock
enemy teams all out there's a bouncer
might be going wide here comes a beamer
how about a daisy cutter that's a Yorker
man of the match leg before Wicket it's
a Bastion take cover
objectives did hardly break us with
objectives leaving the station All
Aboard I could probably use some backup
keep at it we're wearing down the
objective
scrap the objective destroy the
objective we have to protect the
objective to your right on the right on
your left from the left my zone Nicks
are rigged to explode and bring down the
castle door my new creation the zombie
deer will reign fiery death upon you our
teammates down it wasn't my fault I
swear our teammates down I think they
did here I am almost there just keep at
it I'm over here come on get up and I
thought I was supposed to be the comic
relief
I feel a sweet verse coming on give me a
beat
[Music]
g'day mate hi a puzzling prognostication
now back to Natasha for a look at the
weather Jamison Fox interviewing this
fancy robot any wisdom to share with us
as the battle begins I gotcha right okay
sure
group up here join up with me prank with
all due respect my lady I believe that's
a knock against the junkertown education
system
she's the best in the outback join me
pie whoa Mania that one I'm still saying
it for can you boost me like this all
the time your magic death beam
privileges have been rescinded
satelliteian accuracy
too right that ain't mine either die if
you can't handle the heat stay out of
the kitchen